israel21c.org 2019-04-07

# ISRAEL21c Privacy Policy | ISRAEL21c

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ISRAEL21c collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.israel21c.org and https://es.israel21c.org website (“Site”).

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**How we use collected information**

ISRAEL21c may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To send you regular newsletters and email updates_  
If you elect to subscribe to the ISRAEL21c newsletter, we will use your email address to contact you with regular newsletter and Site updates. In this case, your email address is stored on a special email delivery system – and you can remove yourself from our list at any time by unsubcribing.
  * _To offer you special downloads or participation in competitions_
  * If you decide to participate and fill in the details, we will use your information for statistics analysis and may contact you by email regarding the purpose for which you filled in your information.
  * _To run and operate our Site_  
We may need your information to display content on the Site correctly. In which case, the information – such as your location, browser and device – is gathered anonymously and is not stored on our servers.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

ISRAEL21c has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please click here to contact us.

_This policy was created originally with the generator at[PrivacyPolicies.com](https://www.privacypolicies.com/). The policy was last updated on May 23, 2018_
